

www.uttapong.com uttapong@gmail.com (66) 89-485-2280

I'm front-end and back-end web developer with 8 years of professional experience. I'm interested in new technologies of web development frameworks or libraries and new graphics design trend and my major focus is on designing web, mobile & tablet interfaces. I also have skills in other fields like Java, Python, Database and Computer admistration.

EDUCATION

2001 Information Technology, Master of Science

Sirindhorn International Institute of Technology (SIIT),

Thammasat University

Thailand Mutation and Variation database (ThaiMUT)

2006 Computer Engineering, Bachelor of Engineering

Faculty of Engineering, Thammasat UniversityAn online questionaire using XML and Web Services



EXPERIENCE

BIOTEC, NSTDA, Thailand Nov 2013 - Present

Research Asssistant

Bioinformatics Tools and algorithms development (Thalassemia Interpretation Tools, Mutation Annotation Tools) and High

performance computer adminstration.

RingZero (on Srisawat, Bank of Ayudhaya site) Oct 2012 - Oct 2013 Software Engineer

Develop and maintenance in-house software to support Bank

process. National Bureu Credits Checking System,

iChecker-An integrated system of mobile app and web application to check customer information. Branch Profile-Branch information application, Branch Activity-Application to records working logs for

all employees.

Sanook Online Limited
Dec 2011 - Oct 2012

Senior Programmer

Develop and maintenance http://playtown.sanook.com,

http://game.sanook.com for both front-end and back-end website

including developer's API and CMS(Expression Engine)

Absolute Achita

Oct 2010 - Nov 2011

Senior Programmer

Game online system development, Front-end and Back-end Web

developer/Web design.

BIOTEC, NSTDA, Thailand

Apr 2006 - Sep 2010

Research Asssistant

High Performance Computer Administrator (Unix, MacOSX Server, Solaris) Database Administrator, Bioinformatics research in following topic: Gene database mining and analyzation, Bioinformatics

Software and algorithms Development.

PROFICIENCY

Node js, Express: Advanced

PHP (Laravel,CI,CakePHP): Expert

Angular: Advanced

React: Advancedt

Java: Basic

Python: Expert

Database (MySQL, Mongo, Redis, pgsQL): Advanced

Adobe Illustrator: Advanced

HTML/CSS: Expert



NOV 2013

AIS 1-2-3 Young Cyber Designer Awards

Gold Awards: Emoticon design













Beer

Videogames





FEB 2007

PUBLICATIONS

MAR 2010 MUTation ANnotation Tool (MUTANT) Uttapong Ruangrit, Anunchai Assawamakin, Chumpol Ngamphiw, Bunyarit Uyyanonvara, Sissades Tongsima.. Asian Young Researchers Conference on Computational and Omics Biology 2010, March 10-12, 2010.

PEC 2009 **RExPrimer:** an integrated primer designing tool increases PCR effectiveness by avoiding 3' SNP-in-primer and mis-priming from structural variation Jittima Piriyapongsa, Chumpol Ngamphiw, Anunchai Assawamakin, Pongsakorn Wangkumhang, Payiarat Suwannasri, Uttapong Ruangrit, Gallissara Agavatpanitch, Sissades Tongsima.8th International Conference on Bioinformatics (InCoB2009), 2009.

NOV 2009 **pHCR: a parallel haplotype configuration reduction algorithm for haplotype interaction analysis**. Wattanan Makarasara, Natsuhiko Kumasaka, Anunchai Assawamakin, Atsushi Takahashi, Apichart Intarapanich, Chumpol Ngamphiw, Supasak Kulawonganunchai, Uttapong Ruangrit, Suthat Fucharoen, Naoyuki Kamatani, Sissades Tongsima. J Hum Genet. 2009 Nov;54(11):634-41.

AUG 2008 Thailand mutation and variation database (ThaiMUT) Uttapong Ruangrit, Metawee Srikummool, Anunchai Assawamakin, Chumpol Ngamphiw, Suparat Chuechote, Vilasinee Thaiprasarnsup, Gallissara Agavatpanitch, Ekawat Pasomsab, Pa-Thai Yenchitsomanus, Surakameth Mahasirimongkol, Wasun Chantatita, Passit Palittapangarpaim, Rupyarit Hayangayara, Chanin Limyangga, Sicandor, Tangrima, Human Mutation 08 (2009) 20 (2019) 375

Chantratita, Prasit Palittapongarnpim, Bunyarit Uyyanonvara, Chanin Limwongse, Sissades Tongsima. Human Mutation 08/2008; 29(8):E68-75.
D0I:10.1002/humu.20787.

WASP: a Web-based Allele-Specific PCR assay designing tool for detecting SNPs and mutations Pongsakorn Wangkumhang, Kridsadakorn Chaichoompu, Chumpol Ngamphiw, Uttapong Ruangrit, Juntima Chanprasert, Anunchai Assawamakin, Sissades Tongsima. BMC Genomics 02/2007; 8:275. DOI:10.1186/1471-2164-8-275